Aitor Lozano

I'm a freelance game developer at <u>PlayMedusa</u>. I'm from the Canary Islands (Spain), and I have a piece of paper saying that I'm a "Computer Science Engineer".

I'm mostly interested in programming, specially anything related with videogames. For the lasts 10 years most of my work has been related with Unity3D development, and eventually, websites including smartcontract development.

Experience

PlayMedusa

Game Developer · Jun 2011 - Current

At <u>PlayMedusa</u> we work on something we love, from home, enjoying the flexible timetable that such a creative activity requires.

We offer third party development services while making our own games in our spare time.

Some of our games



OUR LATEST SERVICES



Teaching at EOI

Teacher · April 2022 - July 2022

A 110 hours video game development course at the Escuela de Organización Industrial, where we developed several minigames to learn about Unity, C#, design patterns and gamefeel.

Teaching at ULPGC

External teacher · Oct 2014 - Jun 2020

University expert in design and game programming at the University of Las Palmas de Gran Canaria. Subjects taught: design patterns, multiplayer, gamefeel, and development workshops.

30 Parallel Games

Lead Developer · Jan 2018 - Jan 2020

Video game development with Unity3D + C# and web technologies.

Published titles:

<u>Bitponies</u>: Blockchain game centered around breedable, collectible and eventually raceable horses.

Relativity Studios

Lead Developer · Jan 2017 - Dec 2017

Mobile video game development with Unity3D + C#

Published titles:

American Girl World (iOS)
Barbie™ You Can Be Anything (iOS)

Education

Universidad de Las Palmas de Gran Canaria

Computer Science Engineer · 2007 - 2013

Skills

Programming Languages

- C#
- JavaScript (React and Node.js)
- Solidity (Hardhat)
- Server backend

Software

- Windows, OSX, Linux
- Unity3D
- Git
- Rider